A Guide to the Larry Levis papers, 1974-2006 M 426
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1974-2006
  - Southern Indiana Review, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Southwick, Marcia, 1974-1983, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Spicer, David, racoon, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Spring Church Book Company, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - St. James Press, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - St. John, David, 1980-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Starkey, David, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Stearns, Kate, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stern, Jenny, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Strand, Mark, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Swenson, Karen, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Syracuse University, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tallent, Elizabeth, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Tate, James, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Terry, Thomas, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Textor, Alex Robertson, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Thorburn, Alex, 1981, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tudor, Amy, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - University of Alabama in Birmingham Poetry Symposium, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, 1980, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - University of California, Irving, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - University of Iowa Press, 1980-1981, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - University of Pittsburgh Press, 1984-1995, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Vasseur, Jeffery, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - W. W. Norton and Company, 1980, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Walker, Ronald, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - White, Mike, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Wood, Renate, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Wright, Charles, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Wright, Franz, 1980-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Writers at Work, 1987, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified correspondence, 1980-1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous envelopes, 1980-1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - James Marshall correspondence: The American Poetry Review, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - James Marshall correspondence: The Antioch Review, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - James Marshall correspondence: Beacon Press, 1997-1998, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - James Marshall correspondence: Contemporary Authors Autobiography Series, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - James Marshall correspondence: Field, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - James Marshall correspondence: Lehman, David, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - James Marshall correspondence: University of Michigan Press, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - James Marshall correspondence: Wenner Media, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: The American Poetry Review, 1996, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Brady, Sheila, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Buckley, Christopher, 1996-2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Dudley, Ellen, The Marlboro Review, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Eastern Washington University Press, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Fagan, Kathy, The Journal, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Field, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Kytle, Rayford, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Lehman, David, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Orr, Gregory, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Pleiades, circa 1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Poetry, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Powell, Jim, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Quarterly West, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Rackin, Ethel, The American Poetry Review, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Rawlinson, Anne, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Rohrbacher, C., 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Salt Hill Journal, 1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Souders, Bruce, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: The Southern Review, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: St. John, David, 1998, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: University of Pittsburgh, 1996-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: Zola, Jim, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Mary Flinn correspondence: unidentified, 1996-2006, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Other correspondence: Brady, Sheila to Barry Weller, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Other correspondence: Flint, Roland to Dave Smith, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Other correspondence: Glenn, Ann to Sheila Brady, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Other correspondence: Kelen, Leslie to Andrew Miller, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Series 2: Writings, circa 1977-1999
  - Subseries 2.1: Collected Works, circa 1977-1999
    - The Afterlife - title page, photograph, circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - "Picking Grapes in an Abandoned Vineyard", undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - poem drafts, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 5, Folder 40-41)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - poem drafts, corrected, and galley pages, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - poem drafts and photocopies of published poems, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - manuscript draft, undated (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - manuscript draft, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - manuscript final, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - galley, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Dollmaker's Ghost - book jackets, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Winter Stars - "Adolescencia," translation by R. Vallarino, circa 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Winter Stars - poem drafts with comments, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Winter Stars - manuscript draft with cover letters, comments, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 1], manuscript drafts and poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 2], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 3], poem drafts and proofs, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 4], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 5], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 6], poem drafts, corrected, and letter from Sheila Brady, 1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 7], manuscript draft and poem drafts, corrected, envelope, and statement, 1983-1984, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 8], manuscript draft with cover letter, and poem drafts, corrected, 1983, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Winter Stars - [Manuscripts 9], manuscript drafts and poem drafts, corrected, with cover letter, 1983, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Winter Stars - proofs, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Winter Stars - book jackets and order forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Widening Spell of Leaves - "At the Grave of my Guardian Angel, St. Louis Cemetary, New Orleans," draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 1], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 2], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 3], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 4], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 5], manuscript drafts and poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 6], manuscript drafts and poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 7], manuscript drafts and poem drafts, corrected, and a letter, 1991, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 8], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Widening Spell of the Leaves - [Manuscripts 9], poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Black Freckles - "Black Freckles" and "Three Illustrations," drafts, corrected, photocopied, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Black Freckles - "Three Illustrations," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Black Freckles - story drafts, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Black Freckles - manuscript draft with note, I Grandi Fotografi by Josef Koudelka, 1983, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Black Freckles - manuscript drafts, corrected, 1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
    - Black Freckles - proofs, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Elegy - "Anastasia and Sandman," drafts and proofs, corrected, 1994-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Elegy - "The Angel in the Gate," drafts, corrected, 1993-1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Elegy - "Art," drafts, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Elegy - "Because They Cound Not Bind Him Twice," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Elegy - "Bell's Tavern," drafts, corrected, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Elegy - "Boy in Video Arcade," drafts, corrected, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Elegy - "Carte de l'Assassin A.M. Andre Breton," drafts, 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Elegy - "Clear Day," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Elegy - "Col Tempo," drafts, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Elegy - "The Cook Grew Lost in his Village, the Village in the Endless Shuffling of Their Cards," drafts, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Elegy - "Da Li Vi Imate Kartu Za Trieste? Nema? Da Li Vi Imate New York Herald Tribune?," draft, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Elegy - "Elegy Ending in the Sound of a Skipping Rope," drafts, corrected, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Elegy - "Elegy for the Infinite Wrapped in Tinfoil," drafts, 1992-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Elegy - "Elegy for Poe with the Music of a Carnival Inside It," drafts, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Elegy - "Elegy for Whatever Had a Pattern in It," drafts, circa 1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with a Bridle in its Hand," drafts, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with a Chimneysweep Still Falling Through It," drafts, corrected, 1994-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with a Petty Thief in the Rigging," drafts, corrected, 1993-1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with a Thimble Full of Water in a Cage," drafts, corrected, 1994-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with a Trapeze Inside It," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with the Rumpled Apron of a Dishwasher Thrown into It," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Elegy - "Elegy with the Sprawl of a Wave Inside It," drafts, corrected, 1994-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Elegy - "Even the Streets and Trees Grow Lost in the Translation," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Elegy - "Francois Villon on the Cross of Time," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Elegy - "Ghost Confederacy," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Elegy - "God is Always Seventeen," drafts, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Elegy - "Green, Green, How Ambivalent my Feelings Have Become for You," draft, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Elegy - "Homage to Willie Mays," drafts, corrected, 1992-1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Elegy - "Idle Companion," drafts, corrected, 1992-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Elegy - "If Flesh Could Talk," draft, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Elegy - "If He Came & Diminished Me & Mapped My Way," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Elegy - "In 1967," drafts, 1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Elegy - "In Theory," draft, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Elegy - "Invisible in a Butternut Camouflage of Leaves," drafts, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Elegy - "Invisible in Butternut on Church Hill," draft, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Elegy - "La Strada," drafts, corrected, 1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Elegy - "Late September in Ulcinj," draft, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Elegy - "Little America; Two Littler College Stingy Types?," drafts, corrected, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Elegy - "The Necessary Angel," drafts, corrected, 1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Elegy - "The Necessary Angel" and "Poem Ending with a Hotel on Fire," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Elegy - "Ocean Park No. 17, 1968: Homage to Diebenkorn," drafts, corrected, 1993-1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Elegy - "The Oldest Living Thing in L.A.," drafts, 1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Elegy - "The Orchard," drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Elegy - "Poem Ending with a Hotel on Fire," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Elegy - "She Said," drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Elegy - "A Singing in the Rocks," drafts, corrected, 1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Elegy - "The Smell of the Sea," drafts, corrected, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Elegy - "The Space," drafts, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Elegy - "The Space the Angel Left," drafts, corrected, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Elegy - "The Student," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Elegy - "The Thief in the Painting," drafts, corrected, 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Elegy - "The Two Trees," drafts, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Elegy - "The Worm in the Ear," drafts, corrected, 1994-1995, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Elegy - [Poems Four Lines or Less], drafts, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Elegy - [Short Elegies], drafts, corrected, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Elegy - [Stories, Long Prose Pieces], drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Elegy - [Various Short Poems], drafts, corrected, 1992-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, 1994-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, corrected, 1992-1996, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 2-4)
    - Elegy - list of poem drafts in Black Binders, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Elegy - poem drafts [Black Binder A], corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - Elegy - poem drafts [Black Binder B], corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
    - Elegy - poem drafts [File Drawer 4], corrected, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, corrected, photocopied, 1993-1996, undated (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, corrected, photocopied, and correspondence, 1992-1996, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, corrected, photocopied sets, 1992-1996, undated (Box 14-15, Folder 4-1)
    - Elegy - poem drafts, photocopied, undated (Box 15, Folder 2-5)
    - Elegy - manuscript draft, corrected, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Elegy - manuscript draft and letter, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Elegy - manuscript drafts, corrected, and comments, undated (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Elegy - book jacket and promotional flyer, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Selected Levis - manuscript draft, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
    - The Gazer Within - "The Comedian in the Work of Mourning" [Mock Mockers After That], drafts, corrected, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - The Gazer Within - "Eden and My Generation," drafts, corrected, circa 1980, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - The Gazer Within - "An Interview by David Wojahn", 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - The Gazer Within - "Oaxaca," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - The Gazer Within - "Oaxaca," "Oaxaca and the Politics of Looking," [On Philip Levine], drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - The Gazer Within - "Oaxaca and the Politics of Looking," proof, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - The Gazer Within - "Some Notes on the Gazer Within," draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - The Gazer Within - "Strange Days: Zbigniew Herbert in Los Angeles," drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - The Gazer Within - "Welcome to Larryland," drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - The Gazer Within - introduction draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - The Gazer Within - manuscript draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
    - The Gazer Within - manuscript draft [uncut], undated (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - The Gazer Within - manuscript draft and author-publisher agreement, 1999, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Gazer Within - manuscript final, undated (Box 18-19, Folder 5-3)
  - Subseries 2.2: Other Works, 1980-1996
    - Assorted writings and related materials [odd pieces, file drawer 2], 1980-1992, undated (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Assorted writings, interviews, and related materials, photocopied, 1980-1994, undated (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Journals, 1986-1994, undated (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
    - Journal excerpts, transcribed, 1986, 1993-1994, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Poem drafts, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 3-9)
    - Poem drafts [bookbag and desk], corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
    - Poem drafts, photocopied, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Poem drafts and related materials, corrected, photocopied, undated (Box 22, Folder 2-5)
    - Poetry: "Elegy with the Blur of a Grandstand Going Past," draft, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Poetry: "If Flesh Could Talk," darft, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Poetry: "A Life," draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Prose: "Little Boy: Baby Brother," draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Prose: "Not Life So Proud...", The Fuehrer Bunker, "Waiting for the End of the World...", drafts, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Prose: "Roulette," "An Illustrated Castle," "The Blind Violinist to the Boy...," "Into the Marbling of the Maze," and other drafts, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Prose: "So That: On Holub's 'Meeting Ezra Pound'" and other drafts, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Prose: "War as Parable and War as Fact," drafts, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Prose drafts, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Prose and poem drafts, corrected, 1993, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Prose and poem drafts, corrected, undated (Box 23-24, Folder 7-1)
    - Prose and poem drafts [file drawer 4], corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Prose, poem, and play drafts [Morello], corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified drafts, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
    - Unidentified drafts [handwritten pieces], corrected, undated (Box 24-25, Folder 6-1)
    - Unidentified drafts [handwritten pieces, file drawer 4], corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
    - Unidentified drafts [uncollected poems], corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified drafts [writing, file drawer 4], corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2.3: Writings of Others, 1985-1999
    - Anonymous, "Chapter Three", undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Becerra, Jose Carlos, "Dark Word, to my sisters," translated by Robert L. Jones, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Bell, Marvin, "Someone is Probably Dead", undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Fenza, D. W., "The Wish to be Swept Clean: The Poetry of Larry Levis", undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Glass, L., [untitled], 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Glenn, Ann, "That Summer of Ellen", undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Hudgins, Andrews, Saints and Strangers, circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Jacobstein, Roy, Dispersion and Cohesion: Associative Techniques in Poems of Andre Breton, Mary Ruefle, and Larry Levis, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Levine, Philip, "The Mortal Words of Zweik", undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Philip, "My Mother's First Poem", undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Levine, Philip, "One Brother Said to the Other, 'Let's Go into the Fields'", undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Lux, Thomas, "Thus, He Spoke His Quietus - For Larry Levis (1946-1996)", circa 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Smiddy, Nina, untitled poetry manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Snyder, Gary, "Above Pate Valley", undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - St. John, David, Study for the World's Body: New and Selected Poems, poem drafts, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Voigt, Ellen Bryant, Kyrie, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Whedon, Tony, "The Death of Russ Columbo", undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Whedon, Tony, "The Porch", undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - White, Michael interview with Larry Levis, drafts, corrected, circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified poems, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Series 3: Printed Materials, 1980-2005
  - Advertisements mentioning Larry Levis, 1989-1999 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  - Articles and press releases about Larry Levis, 1982-2005, undated (Box 26, 39, Folder 18, 3-4)
  - Articles about Philip Levine, 1983, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Brodsky, Joseph, "Odysseus to Telemachus", undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Dana, Robert, "Wildebeest," The Georgia Review, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Graham, Jorie, "A Poetry Reading," booklet, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - The J. Peterman Company, Owner's Manual No. 38a, Fall, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Jewish Community Center, Kansas City, press release, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Kelen, Leslie, "After the Obsession with some Beloved Figure: an Interiew with Larry Levis", 1990 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Nancy Drysdale Gallery, "Elizabeth King: Illusion of Conciousness," exhibit flyer, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - New Virginia Review, Remembering Larry Levis, flyer, circa 1996 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Poetry: "Anastasia and Sandman & Other Poems," American Poetry Review, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Poetry: "The Smell of the Sea," American Poetry Review, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Poetry: "The Thief in the Painting," American Poetry Review, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - The Poetry Center, reading program, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Prose: "From 'Not Life So Proud to Be Life: Snodgrass, Rothenberg, Bell, and the Counter-Revolution," The Poetry of W.D. Snodgrass, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Prose: "Larry Levis, 1946 -," Contemporary Authors Autobiography Series, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Prose: "Not Life So Proud To Be Life: Snodgrass, Rothenberg, Bell, and the Counter-Revolution," The American Poetry Review, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Prose: "Philip Levine," On the Poetry of Philip Levine, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Prose: "So That: On Holub's 'Meeting Ezra Pound,'" Field, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Prose: "Some Notes on Grief and the Image," Of Solitude and Silence: Writings on Robert Bly, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Prose: "Some Notes on the Gazer Within," Field and A Field Guide to Contemporary Poetry and Poetics, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Prose: "Strange Days: Zbigniew Herbert in Los Angeles," The Antioch Review, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Prose: "Takže: o Holubove 'Setkáni s Ezrou Poundem'" and Miroslav Holub "Setkáni s Ezrou Poundem," Ezra Pound: Mistr Tech, Kterí Vedí, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Prose: "War as Parable and War as Fact: Herbert and Forch?," American Poetry Review, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Reviews, 1981-2001 (Box 27, 39, Folder 1, 10)
  - St. John, David, poetry reading flyer, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Tampa Review, flyer, circa 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Vienna city map, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Wright, James, "The Journey", undated (Box 27, Folder 5)